Sabaton, Sabaton, Sabaton
Blackstock, we're Sabaton and this is Ghost Division
This is the way the invasion has begun
Shaking the ground with the force of house and guns
Touching the line of fire
Touching two hostile guns, that's leading the way
Leading the way
Charging the lines with the force of a furious roar
Crashing the lightning and the tongues roaring
200 miles an hour, taking with you not a bus or a mermaid
But a new race to take
They are the pups, we're the lees, born to compete, never retreat
Living or dead, always aware, dead or young again
Always ahead, as if it's Knieveling, just run
Making morale with the sound of blazing gun
Touching the line of fire
Touching two hostile guns, that's leading the way
Leading the way
Leaving the trail of destruction to the foreign land
Kill war on the Transnistrian
The Nazi was shot, in the soul of the Nazi
Death and no sedation
Communications broken
Time is the fire when the soldier live
Burning their fame
They are the pups, we're the lees, born to compete, never retreat
Living or dead, always aware, dead or young again
Thank you, Bloodstock!
They sleep from time for the tremendous force of their ancestors
Reaching the way for a panzer, oh
Choking on their death and death stars
Touching the line of fire
Touching two hostile guns, that's leading the way
Leading the way
They are the pups, we're the lees, born to compete, never retreat
Ghost in the flesh, I am the godhead, always aware, dead or young again
Hounds to their knees, born to compete, never retreat
They're hostile and they're not allowed
Living or dead, always aware, dead or young again
Great!
Demolished and paralyzed, my brother's eyes are gone
And we shall all be buried here, in needless marks and screams
Motherhood, get a telegram, and shed a tear of grief
Motherblood in foreign land, trying to understand
Where is this greatness I've been told?
This is the life that I've been sold
Is this a worthy sacrifice?
Great war, and I cannot take more
Great war, I cannot buy shit, no
This is a great story, that we will not undo
Great war, those who've been in our world
I'm standing here, all fluffy, with bodies set like bees
Over there, the other trench, one leg spread by me
Lead on in, as the captain said, and shoot them over the nose
But when my ears prove on the sand, one tell that I may come
Why do my duties pay the price?
How do the world its sacrifice?
I know my deeds are not in vain
Great war, and I cannot take more
Great war, I cannot buy shit, no
This is a great story, that we will not undo
Great war, those who've been in our world
And feet by feet, we pay the price of blood by the hand
Though men may fall, we seek Jesus Christ
We face the heat, as we are fighting until the dawn
So follow me, and we will write our own history
I cannot take more, great war, I cannot buy shit, no
This is a great story, that we will not undo
Great war, those who've been in our world
Wars come as swiftly, the world is closing in
We're a company of soldiers, with a form we write and style
All alone, stand alone
Our death look rather burning, like a lit up hand
As the blitzkrieg's pushing harder, the war is all around
All around, holy ground
Fight for 18 days, the battles, no one's silent on sight
We will fight for all, until the bullets are gone
We, we will resist and fight, fight hard, cause we are gold inside
We, we take our bombs and fight, fight hard, resist and do what's right
No matter how tight it is, the god will cease to count
They don't doubt, and if you cannot keep us, put a new and true flag of failure
We fought hard, and the war was over, and the war is over
But we'll keep to the very essence, the force to tell the truth
We were chosen by the slayer, we will surprise them with a laugh
We are harder than gold, we were harder than gold
We were told to hold the border, and that is what we did
Our new world is seen despite all that glow
We, we will resist and fight, fight hard, cause we are gold inside
We, we take our bombs and fight, fight hard, resist and do what's right
Though we are fought with spears, the dead have closed their doors
And they're suited to Moses, the poor are their slavers
We, we will resist and fight, fight hard, cause we are gold inside
We, we take our bombs and fight, fight hard, resist and do what's right
Oh, my friends, pardon my language, but it's so fucking good to be back
Ten years ago, we stood on this stage for the first time
We had 20 minutes, it was round about lunchtime or something like that
And I remember the people who were in the front row
Were all pretty damn hungover, okay, or hungover, sorry
And I remember when I asked you to headbang, you all headbanged once
Then you realized how much beer you had the night before
So, however, we do have a little bit more than 20 minutes tonight
We're gonna go all in and do 30 minutes for you guys
Cause we're such nice Swedish guys
Anyway, we're gonna do a bit of a mix here
But obviously we just released a new album called The Great War
So there will be some stuff from that, there will also be some older stuff
So we're gonna have new shit, old shit, and some songs are just plain shit, so
You want us to play that song?
Let's do Fields of Verdun!
300, the day's spreading on the sun, Fields of Verdun!
Then the battle has begun, nowhere to run
Father and son, all one by one
Under their gun, they will be done
Death and justice has begun, nowhere to run
Father and son, all one by one, Fields of Verdun!
Though a million ships have scattered out
The battle has begun, from the crest, the upper hand
From the ground up onto trenches, where the soldiers make their stand
As the trenches slowly turn to blood, and the Greek police start to flood
There's a wait in every corner, to die in the blood, for the trenches of blood
The second, in the darkness
300, the day's spreading on the sun, Fields of Verdun!
Then the battle has begun, nowhere to run
Father and son, all one by one
Under their gun, they will be done
Death and justice has begun, nowhere to run
Father and son, all one by one, Fields of Verdun!
Fields of execution, put away slag from the grass
Thou shalt go no further, it was said, they shall pass
The spirit of resistance and the madness of the war
So go ahead, take your lead, jump to death, or you die playing the...
The second, in the darkness
300, the day's spreading on the sun, Fields of Verdun!
Then the battle has begun, nowhere to
Father and son, all one by one
Under their gun, they will be done
Then the judgment has begun, nowhere to run
Father and son, all one by one, Fields of Verdun!
Alright bloodsuckers, you want more?
Hussars!
The new England starts to grind
Hey! Let's see some hands in the air!
Hey!
A cry for help, a tithe of mead
A weight relieved from holy lead
60 days of siege of Dumberley
Sent a message to the sky, wounded soldiers left to die
Will they hold the wall, or will the siege be gone?
Medication, indigestion, their number, fifty to one
Now the battle has begun, the new England starts to grind
Hey!
Coming down from the mountainside
The new England starts to grind
Coming down with a turn of tide
As the days are passing by, and as the dead are piling high
No escape and no salvation
Trenches to explosive holes, are buried deep beneath the walls
Plant the charges there, and watch the siege be feared
How will you catch the inspiration, the grace against the vile?
The grace against the vile
Now the new England starts to grind
Hey!
Coming down from the mountainside
The new England starts to grind
Hey!
Coming down with a turn of tide
Shivering bolts are coming down from the sky
Jenny says, are you ready to die?
With this you'll never know the sign for a ride
We'll be swept up from the steps of our gates
All this fear will be facing our fate
Like a corvus of the ceiling of fate
Remember, it's September, as the wind's been yelling
Now a spring, we may be in the mid-year
But the wind does start to rise
Are you ready still?
You're coming down from the mountainside
Hey!
The wind does start to rise
Coming down with a turn of tide
Coming down from the mountainside
The wind does start to rise
Coming down with
Coming down with a turn of tide
We remember, it's September, when the wind does start to rise
In the drought of 1917, our land was from tender seed
Overseas through the trenches we went, from the land of the free
Into war he brought two things along, a life full of disbelief
John the writer supplied the site to 328
There, on that day, down in New York, they entered the frame
Saving the day, they too said, but not aware
Into the fires of hell they had gone, not a hero to be
Entered the war from overseas, they came in 1984, the way through the demise
The fires of hell, the demise, built in 123
When his fate has been put to the test, the call to arms he hears
On the 8th of October he went, made a sergeant for his deeds
There is bleeding, the rain of the war, machine gun on the hill
Judge the enemy, take him, but we still have the power of his will
There, on that day, sergeants flocked, they entered the frame
Saving the day, they too said, but not aware
Into the fires of hell they had gone, not a hero to be
Entered the war from overseas, intervened 1918, the way through the demise
Into 123
What sergeant York achieved that day, records from the USA
It's 82nd all the way, gets from above, but they now say
It's 82nd all the way, gets from above,
Into the fires of hell they had gone, not a hero to be
Entered the war from overseas, intervened 1918, the way through the demise
Into 123
What sergeant York achieved that day, records from the USA
It's 82nd all the way, gets from above, but they now say
Into the fires of hell they had gone, not a
Entered the war from overseas, intervened 1918, the way through the demise
Into 123
In the sound of a machine gun, they didn't go in the night
Mortars firing, rains the scene, scars the fields, and ones who agreed
The stalemate had the throat high, where the Soviets rested mad
The story should be won, but many men will suffer, know that many men will die
Half a million lives at stake, at the fields, bomb has set bail
As the night falls, the general calls, and the battle chariot's drawn
And on, what is the purpose of it all?
Once a price of a mile, thousands of feet march to the beat
It's an army on the march, long away from home
Day in the progress, in young men's lives, thousands of feet march to the beat
It's an army in despair, kneeling in mud
Stuck in a cage with no way out
Thousands of machine guns, kept on firing during the night
Mortars blaze, and wreck the scene, dumps the fields, and ones who agreed
Still a deadlock at the front line, where the soldiers died mad
Rooms and houses seem swung on, still no glory has been won
Know that many men have suffered, know that many men have died
Six miles of ground has been won, half a million men are gone
And as the men call, the general calls, the killing carried on
And on, what is the purpose of it all?
Once a price of a mile, thousands of feet march to
It's an army on the march, long away from home
Day in the progress, in young men's lives, thousands of feet march to the beat
It's an army in despair, kneeling in mud
Stuck in a cage with no way out
Young men are dying, they pay the price
Oh, how they suffer, so kill me
Once a price of a mile, there's a price for a mile
Thousands of feet march to the beat, it's an army on the march
Long away from home, day in the progress, in young men's lives
Thousands of feet march to the beat, it's an army in despair
Kneeling in mud, stuck in a trench with no way out
Thousands of feet march to the beat, it's an army on the march
Long away from home, day in the progress, in young men's lives
Thousands of feet march to the beat, it's an army in despair
Kneeling in mud, stuck in a trench with no way out
Thousands of feet march to the beat, it's an army on the march
Long away from home, day in the progress, in young men's lives
Thousands of feet march to the beat, it's an army in despair
Kneeling in mud, stuck in a trench with no way out
From the mist, a shape, a ship is taking form
And the silence of the seas are bound to drift into a storm
Sign of power, show of force
Raise the anchor, battle ships, floating its course
Crane of a nation, a beast made of steel
This marking motion, king of the ocean
It was made to rule the waves across the seven seas
To lead the war machine, to rule the waves and lead the Kriegsmarine
The terror of the seas, the Bismarck and the Kriegsmarine
Two thousand men and fifty thousand tons of steel
Set the course for the Atlantic with the Allies on their heels
Firepower, firefight
Battle stations, keep your targets set in sight
Interformation, the heart has begun
Kill that damnation
The fleet is coming, it was made to rule the waves across the seven seas
To lead the war machine, to rule the waves and lead the Kriegsmarine
The terror of the seas, the Bismarck and the Kriegsmarine
Bottom of the ocean, the depths of the abyss
They're bound by the flagship of the navy
The terror of the seas, these guns have been silent at last
Crane of a nation, a beast made of steel
This marking motion, king of the ocean
It was made to rule the waves across the seven seas
To lead the war machine, to rule the waves and lead the Kriegsmarine
The terror of the seas, the Bismarck and the Kriegsmarine
The terror of the seas, Bismarck and the Kriegsmarine
To lead the war machine, to rule the waves and lead the Kriegsmarine
Thank you very much, I'm so impressed
You know, the hospitality, the local crew, everyone involved in making Bloodstock happen
Are really fucking good people, so will you please all make some noise for Bloodstock
Alright, how about a little bit more heavy metal
How about something with a hammered organ
How about something about a pirate
How about the Red Baron
Now you're a shield, you're not a bed, between the fighting circus of the man from Russia
Tie up, clean, the spike of man's ego, paint the rest of the continent all the way to Russia
You're from above, you're under fire
Stained with his blood, disrobing higher
Though I'm a soldier, throw the horse back to the skies
Then the legend will arise
And he's flying higher, he came from the sky
He's flying to Pasta and he's flying to Nye, higher
But I'm far on Nye, the legend will never die
First to the seas, so these are machines, gladiator and the giant's third
Fire and bullets, they're ready with the kills, ready to face the dominant, it's burning
Let me face the famous squadron leader
Call on this name, let the country go
In the gate to win, a gambler runs the dice
The alien lights pay the price
And he's flying higher, he came from the sky
He's flying to Pasta and he's flying to Nye, higher
But I'm far on Nye, the legend will never die
Fire!
Alright, let's make some noise together my friends
One, two, one, two, three, four, higher
Higher
One more time
He came from the sky, he's flying to Pasta and he's flying to Nye, higher
But I'm far on Nye, the legend will never die
Higher
Born a soldier from the horseback to the skies
And the legend never dies
And he's flying, and he's flying, and he's flying, higher
He came from the sky, flying to Pasta and he's flying to Nye, higher
But I'm far on Nye, the legend will never die
Higher
He came from the sky, flying to Pasta and he's flying to Nye, higher
But I'm far on Nye, the legend will never die
A time of religion and war, let us tell the tale of a lion
This beast in the shape of a man, with a dream to rule sea and land
And all those who stand in his way, die by God, in victorious arms
The righteous that follows, sounds his moan, it is your due
Victims have taught, that those fought, this lion is no fear at all
Lion of hope, comes from the north, from the north
You starve us, by going first, we fear our heads, we fear our hearts
Our cherry books, they tingle, our goose stop, our rock will stop
A story of Europe, a fish farmer, a dream of destruction
The power of the crown of freedom, in a capital he's able to take
The future of our fatherland, show the way, it was still war today
The leader of that mass, featuring that guns, was no easy foe
A story so bold, truth unfold, with truth of the union of peoples
He loved the lion and king, lion and king
You starve us, by going first, we fear our heads, we fear our hearts
Our cherry books, they tingle, our goose stop, our rock will stop
Mighty eagle, rule alone liberator
Take the lion from the north Atlantic, the sector from his head
Mighty eagle, rule alone
And so start this lion, the storm, the bearer of the heart
Lion come forth, come from the north, come from the north
You starve us, by going first, we fear our heads, we fear our hearts
Our cherry books, they tingle, our goose stop, our rock will stop
All is ready
All embrace me, it's my time to rule at last
Fifteen years have I been waiting to sing it out for my brood
No allegiance, I will swing a wolf
Crowned by God, not by the church, as my power makes me right
It's hard, I was too young to rule the land, just as they failed to understand, boy, to rule
My time to pass, but I was chosen by heaven
Say my name when you pray to the sky
To the sky, it's the God of all the skies
With a law, my protector, make it bow to my will
Brooding battle, led my men to victory
No man alive or dead commands me, I answer to the Lord
Hear my order, question me and die
What I say was said in heaven, the soul is shall be done
No, I was destined to rule alone, all for myself, I am claimed to throne, born to rule
My time to pass, but I was chosen by heaven
Say my name when you pray to the sky
To the sky, it's the God of all the skies
With a law, my protector, make it bow to my will
All the sky shall be mine, there's no stopping me
All over Europe, my rule shall be questioned by God
All I seek and to me, that is my decree
My will be done
But I was too young to rule alone, just as they failed to understand what to know
My time is now, I was chosen by heaven
Say my name when you pray to the sky
To the sky, it's the God of all the skies
To the sky, with a law, my protector, make it bow to my will
Rise!
From the depths of hellish silence, bastard spells, explosive violence
Russian minds have my protected, glorious mission undetected
Put down in all the flames, I'm going strong, I'm half-moon's number one
Talking with the moon, looking for the truth, I'm moon's number one
You can hide, you can move, just to write, learn to expect, learn to think dark
Silence is the night, the witch is in the fight, never miss the mark
Canvas, wings of death, the pattern is your fate
Night on the regiment, 188
Undetected, unexpected, wings of glory, tell the story
Deviation, deviation, undetected, stealth, perfected
Silence in ground, retreated to the sound, helpless in the air
Suddenly appears, the world in your face, mindful, the witch is there
Let it fall, come around, I don't sound so, we're about to drown
Lashes, standing high, the old genie awaits, the beaten at the gates
Just to fight and fly
Canvas, wings of death, the pattern is your fate
Night on the regiment, 188
Undetected, unexpected, wings of glory, tell the story
Deviation, deviation, undetected, stealth, perfected
Beneath the starlight of the heavens
Unlikely heroes in disguise
Canvas, wings of death, the witch is gonna die
Stay in fear, humble horizon
Win when wisdom, and the night witch has come
Undetected, unexpected, wings of glory, tell the story
Deviation, deviation, undetected, stealth, perfected
From the depths of hell in silence, lost in spells, explosive violence
Russian beta, but perfected, bonus mission, undetected
Vision of fire, of men, of wax, of sound, of human flesh
Soul connects me, fire gives sign of my desperation
All these sounds, echo in my mind, misconducted by death himself
They all come together as music, the rhythm of
The rhythm of death
A sense of hope
From the land, as they may just stand, they so strong, yet the legend still lives on
1918, the great war, great to some
A battalion is lost in the, my god, hell
Under fire, there's nothing they can do
There's no way they can get a message through
Suffering, they're in losses, but the battle carries on
Liberty, division, standing strong
From the land, as they may just stand, a disregard of the man
It's a rather long die, and the stakes are high
In what they die, there's no time for goodbye
Weapon in hand, as they may just stand, to disregard the demand
Then it never comes why they would rather die
Through the blood, they will finally be saved
25, the ammunition's running low
The supplies, they were dropped off on the floor
1918, the war still, great to some
The battalion's trapped in the, my god, hell
Chose not to surrender, they chose victory or defeat
War and blood, they're blessed in by their fate
From the land, as they may just stand, a disregard of the man
It's a rather long die, and the stakes are high
In what they die, there's no time for goodbye
Weapon in hand, as they may just stand, to disregard the demand
Then it never comes why they would rather die
Through the blood, they will finally be saved
From the land, as they may just stand, a disregard of the man
It's a rather long die, and the stakes are high
In what they die, there's no time for goodbye
Weapon in hand, as they may just stand, to disregard the demand
Then it never comes why they would rather die
Through the blood, they will finally be saved
Suffering heavy losses, in the great war they stood strong
The memory of the fallen, still inside
From the land, as they may just stand, a disregard of the man
It's a rather long die, and the stakes are high
In what they die, there's no time for goodbye
Weapon in hand, as they may just stand, to disregard the demand
Then it never comes why they would rather die
Through the blood, they will finally be saved
You crazy, crazy people
I'm sorry
You fucking asshole
We said we weren't doing that song this night
Now I totally lost it
I had something planned I wasn't about to tell you
Now it's totally gone
I fucking suck as a frontman
Oh, now I got it, yeah
Lost Battalion, a song about the First World War
Now, I thought, if it's okay with you guys
I'm gonna teach you a fact tonight
Something quite interesting
From the battlefields of World War I
This is a scary fact
There's only 40 years back in history
Until we find the last stand of the samurai
It's the nature of time that the old ways must give in
It's the nature of time that the new ways come sincing
When the new meets the old, it always pans the ancient ways
And as the story told, the old ways go out in a blaze
The circle by a vulture
The end of ancient culture
The dawn of destiny draws near
Imperial force to fight
Face the 500 samurai
For mother and her lover
Fix the Chihuahua, the sword, raise the gun
Bujiro, the game you fight
It's the last stand of the samurai
For mother and her lover
That's when the new ways begins
The way of the warrior comes to an end
That's when
That's when the new ways begins
The ways of the old must not be had
It's the nature of time that the old ways must give in
It's the nature of time that the new ways come sincing
On your throne, surrender
Seek out the old contender
The dawn of destiny is near
Imperial force
Face the 500 samurai
For mother and her lover
Fix the Chihuahua, the sword, raise the gun
Bujiro, the game you fight
It's the last stand of the samurai
For mother and her lover
Till the time we hold on
Only torn and left at the end
No more life, none
Shiromiya boy
Imperial force to fight
Face the 500 samurai
Surrender, hand out numbers
Fix the Chihuahua, the sword, raise the gun
Bujiro, the game you fight
It's the last stand of the samurai
Surrender, hand out numbers
60 to 1, facing the gun
60 to 1, charging the gun
In the heart of policy
In the home of Christianity
The seed of power is in danger
There's a foe of a thousand sorts
The wind abandoned by the lords
The vow from grace will favor back
To the nation, the 189
In the service of heaven
They will take to the holy night
It was year B27
In the service of heaven
They will be judged
For the grace, for the might of the lord
For the hope of the holy
For the faith of the way of the sword
In the rights of glory
For the grace, for the might of the lord
In the name of his glory
For the faith of the way of the sword
God tell the story again
I'm a god of 42
While on the secret avenue
A star of Sant'Angelo is reaching
Now the gods of the holy see
That the gods of Christianity
Are through history as fame
With salvation
And the 189
In the service of heaven
They will take to the holy night
It was 1527
In the rise of the steps to heaven
They will be judged
For the grace, for the might of the lord
For the hope of the holy
For the faith of the way of the sword
In the rights of glory
For the grace, for the might of the lord
In the name of his glory
For the faith of the way of the sword
God tell the story again
Like for salvation
With
Like annihilation
Are you ready for Swedish Pegas?
So when they swore to the Zed
As he hearted the battle
That's when we were coming back
And before the attack
The demon starts to boil in your veins
As you charge
As the fire inside
Ignites and thy blood shed
In the circus of nose
Will it be as for Zed
Will the servant be woken
Then we'll have us
Swedish Pegas
Marching ashore
Forged in fire
By the hammer of Thor
Out from Asgard
Arise, kingship sails
Never to turn back again
The brothers have part
As we will dig through
The no-grouse neber blood
Standing tall
They go with the tar
As they wait in the hall
As the fire inside
Ignites and thy blood shed
In the circus of nose
Will it be as for Zed
Will the servant be woken
Then we'll have us
Swedish Pegas
Marching ashore
Forged in fire
By the hammer of Thor
Out from Asgard
Arise, kingship sails
Never to turn back again
First to the battle
First to the feast
Destiny waiting
No breath
Arrgh, you fucking asshole!
Swedish Pegas
Marching ashore
Forged in fire
By the hammer of Thor
Out from Asgard
Arise, kingship sails
Never to turn back again
January or February
But we're gonna be at Wembley Arena, okay?
So, I hope
Each and every one of you will be there
Yes, we will have lawyers going out
With contracts later for you to sign
Anyway
As we're getting closer and closer to the end
It is
Oh, we're not really there yet
You know how this works
Just
Well, yeah, let's start with you
Most important people
Thank you all for an absolutely fantastic evening, Bloodstock
Always a pleasure to be here
As I said earlier
Once again
Give it up for Bloodstock and the Bloodstock crew!
And
Yeah, let's try this
I've seen Bruce Dickinson do this shit
I've seen Bruce Dickinson do this shit on TV
A short man from Texas
A man of the wild
Thrown into combat
With bodies set high
Height, gist, emotions
His blood's running cold
His hikes ripped through his story
And falls
But I ask
How likely
If there be any glory in war
Let it rest
On his leg here
Who would do that?
We can't buy
Colossus from the Nazi yoke
A lone soldier's sleep
Under a metal six-feet thing
A deathless wake
Where snow will be made
Such heart-rending attack
Pull him to the metal and back
A man of his 50's
A man of stand-due
Flesh all around him
A man of his 50's
And yet he ain't through
Let them fall face down
Each day they must die
Make it easier
To say goodbye
Bright, how I'd like
If there be any glory in war
Let it rest
On his leg here
Till the people never came back
Colossus from
A lone soldier's sleep
Under a metal six-feet thing
A deathless wake
Where snow will be made
Such heart-rending attack
Pull him to the metal and back
Vote down the wrong me
And listen while I speak
Oh, but hell, it's six-feet deep
And all along the shore
Where cannons still roar
They're haunting my dreams
They're still there when I sleep
And I'm not sure
What I can do
He's Colossus from the Nazi yoke
A lone soldier's sleep
Under a metal six-feet thing
A deathless wake
Where snow will be made
Such heart-rending attack
Pull him to the metal and back
Don't stop
Thank you for your fantastic evening
I hope we'll meet again
Very soon
At Wembley Arena, my friends
Thank you
Thank you all
And enjoy the rest of the festival