Destruction through a foreign land
To the world of destruction
In the sun of the galaxy
They are the
BOMBS OF THE ENEMIES
Of the never-ending fate
They are the
BOMBS
OF THE ENEMIES
Brothers eyes are dark
Nameless boxes gray
And their shadows
Oh, oh, oh
The last way we go
The fourth is the last
The third is the last
In Blomstock
And I remember the people who were in the front row
Were all pretty damn hangover, okay, or hungover, sorry
And I remember when I asked you to headbang
You all headbanged once
Then you realized how much bigger you had the night before
So, however, we do have a little bit more than 20 minutes tonight
We're gonna go all in and do 30 minutes with you guys
Because we're such nice Swedish guys
Anyway, we're gonna do a bit of a mix here
Obviously we just released a new album called The Great War
So there will be some stuff from that
There will also be some older stuff
So we're gonna have new shit, old shit
And some songs are just plain shit
You want us to play that song?
Let's do Fields of Verdun!
It's what we're done
Her songs!
Another winter solstice
50 days of siege of number three
Sends a message to the wounded soldiers
Let's provide, will they hold the wall for the win?
No escape and no salvation
The walls and the charges them
And watch the CSPF
Coming down the mountain
1917, overseas to the train
In 1980, time of move
With the sound of our machine gun
Inite
Mortars firing, rings to seed
Scars the fields, and ones were green
This is stalemate at the front line
Where the soldiers rest in mud
Roads and houses, all is gone
There's no glory to be won
Now the many men will suffer
Now the many men will die
Life's at stake
And the fields are passion-filled
As the night falls, the general falls
And the battle can't
What is the purpose of it all?
What's the price of a mile?
Doesn't something through the page
It's a march, don't wait
Guys in yellow and black
Through the page, it's a novel
In the spare, knee-deep
Thousands of machine guns
Get them firing through the night
Mortars blazed, erect the scene
Scars the fields, and ones were green
Still a deadlock at the front line
Where the soldiers die in mud
Roads and houses, six long gone
Still no glory has been won
Now the many men have suffered
Six miles of ground has been won
Help us all, we're on the other side
Bit much to the beat
It's an army on the march
Long way from home
Pay the price, young man's lies
House is up, bit much to the beat
It's an army in the spare
Knee-deep, in mud
With no way out
In a trench with no way out
From the mist, a shape, a ship
Is taking form
And the silence of the seas
Are bound to drift into a storm
Sight of power
Sure for battleships
Floating its course
Crying of our mages
Mocking for a thousand men
Any thousand torches of steel
Trap the cores, or lay Atlantic
With the allies on their heels
Battle stations keep the targets
They're being silenced
In depths of the abyss
They're bound by iron and bloody navy
The terror of the seas
Is guns and then silent at last
Missed again the Christmas Eve
This is the best festival in the UK, at least for me personally
You know, the hospitality, the local crew, everyone involved in making Bloodstock happen
Are really fucking good people, so will you please all make some noise for Bloodstock!
Alright, how about a little bit more heavy metal?
How about something with a hammered organ?
How about something about a pirate?
And it's flying
Higher
The king of the sky
The life of our crew
And it's flying
Higher
The king of the sky
Let's make some noise together my friends
One, two, one, two, three, four
Higher
One more time
And it's flying
Higher
The king of the sky
Our horses stand in his soul
We're ready to be the sceptre
You ready for Carola's Wrex?
Face me
Last 50 years have I been waiting
To see it all coming through
Guns, rifles with a wound
I was close to my head
Well, say my name
Question me, you don't
What I say was said in heaven
And so I've started up
All for myself
I am
I was chosen by heaven
Say my name when you pray
To the sky sector
I see Carola's Wrex
Big question right now
It sounds better still
Interstand is the strong and the legend still lives on
The
And
Yeah, let's try this.
I've seen Bruce Dickens on the shit on TV.